so this is ramo pontiac and he said please start promoting the general strike on may 21st and i
say y'all will do everything but revolt and he said wtf a central strike is you know i have
seriously followed you for so long and the fact that nobody is radical enough for you when you're
just flapping your guns is really freaking is flapping your gums is really freaking frustrating
well guess what you white people are not radical enough for me you're fucking right you're not
you know who the radicals are the people in england who actually got arrested and were put
in prison for trying to shut down elbert systems that's radical y'all want to do everything but
revolt y'all want to dance at protests y'all want to make sign parties and then you want to accuse me
of only flapping my gums i have a fucking time i just got back from cuba so don't tell me about
flapping my gums me and my gums are doing more to decolonize minds than you sitting up here
on my instagram telling me about promoting a general strike y'all will do everything
you